// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "In a decomposition reaction,",
    answer: "energy in the form of heat or light is often produced",
    options: [
      "one of the rectants is often water",
      "energy in the form of heat or light is often produced",
      "the rectants are usually are a metal or non-metal",
      "the reactants is usually two ionic compunds in aqueous solution"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The chemical equation, KClO3 -> KCl + O2, is an example of which type of reaction?",
    answer: "Decompostion",
    options: [
      "Double Displacement",
      "Single Displacement",
      "Combustion",
      "Decompostion"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: " In the following chemical reaction, what product is represented by X? AlCl3 + NaOH -> X + NaCl",
    answer: "Al(OH)3",
    options: [
      "AlOH",
      "Al(OH)3",
      "Al3OH",
      "It cannot be determined."
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Combination reactions always:",
    answer: "form only one product",
    options: [
      "involve an element and an ionic compound",
      "use only one reactant",
      "require oxygen gas",
      "form only one product"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: " Which of the following is an example of a chemical reaction?",
    answer: " Photosynthesis in plants",
    options: [
      "The break down of food into energy",
      " Photosynthesis in plants",
      "Metal rusting",
      " All of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What kind of chemical reaction is where two substances combine to make a new substance?",
    answer: "Synthesis reaction",
    options: [
      "Synthesis reaction",
      "Decomposition reaction",
      "Combustion",
      "Photochemical reaction"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What does a catalyst do to a chemical reaction?",
    answer: "Speeds up the rate of reaction",
    options: [
      "Stops the reaction",
      "Starts the reaction",
      "Speeds up the rate of reaction",
      "Slows down the rate of reaction"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Oxidation is a process which involves",
    answer: "addition of oxygen",
    options: [
      "addition of oxygen",
      "addition of hydrogen",
      "removal of oxygen",
      "removal of hydrogen"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The process of reduction involves",
    answer: "addition of hydrogen",
    options: [
      "addition of oxygen",
      "addition of hydrogen",
      "removal of oxygen",
      "removal of hydrogen"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What type of chemical reactions take place when electricity is passed through water?",
    answer: "Decomposition",
    options: [
      "Displacement",
      "Combination",
      "Decomposition",
      "Double displacement"
    ]
  },
  
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];